哦  希希  你们两个又在一起了?
Oh, Cece. Are you two kids
back together?
她想得美
- She wishes.
不 我家里的管道不通  发生了很严重的堵塞
- No, plumbing's out-- severe clogging.
我不该问的
- I'm sorry I asked.
事实就是这样的
- This is what happens.
四个骨瘦如柴的模特
Four models with
protein deficiencies,
一起洗澡
sharing a shower.
(Laughs)
她们脱衣服就像  就像一件4美元的圣诞毛衫
They shed like a... like
a four-dollar Christmas sweater.
亲们 猜猜发生了什么?
Guys, guess what?
我刚刚和一个学生的关系有了突破性进展
I just made a breakthrough
with a student.
这是真的
Yeah, it's true.
哦 别这样
- Don't, please.
呃 杰茜?
- Uh, Jess?
你知道我们都很爱你  我们都支持你
You know we love you,
we all support you...
我与一个学生之间的关系有了突破性进展
♪ I'm breaking through
with students. ♪
但是当你这样做的时候  我很抱歉 往碗里放钱吧
...but when you do things
like this, I'm sorry... bowl.
好吧
Okay.
她还不满足
It's just not satisfying.
我也这么认为
- I think it is.
好吧
- Okay.
你说有了突破性进展
You said you had
a breakthrough.
给大人当老师对我来说就像新的世界一样
It's just a whole new world
teaching adults.
这周我给他们分配了任务
This week, I gave
them an assignment.
我让他们写下来他们想要的任何东西
I said write whatever you want
要加上一点描述性的想象
just load it up
with descriptive imagery.
我蓬松的枕头
My fluffy pillow,
我黄色的蓬松的枕头
my yellowy fluffy pillow,
在我的狗狗旁边  我毛茸茸的狗狗旁边 我挚爱的毛茸茸的狗狗旁边
next to my dog, my hairy dog,
my beloved hairy dog,
虽然我在欺骗我自己
while I diddle myself.
很好
Excellent.
他是一条人鱼
He was a merman.
他是他们种群里最后一条人鱼
He was the last of his kind,
他需要为他的人鱼宝宝找一个妈妈
and he needed a mother
for his mer-child.
他不是一个人鱼绅士
He was not a mer-gentleman.
我已经等不及听下面的内容了
Can't wait to hear more.
我就是和他们无法交流  而我又不知道原因
I just can't connect with them
and I don't know why.
好吧 杰茜  你不应该教他们如何写作
Look, Jess, you can't teach
people how to write.
这不是真的
- Not true.
我是从一个作家的角度来说
- I say that as a writer.
这也不是真的
- Also not true.
一个写作课是为了
- A writing class is for
一些没法抒情的表达自己的想法的人
somebody who doesn't think
lyrically in terms of,
就像诗一般的词语硬生生被绑在一起
like, poetic words
that just... are strung...
你说你和一个学生有了突破性进展
You said you had
a breakthrough.
是的  我有一个学生叫
So I have this student
whose name
埃德加  而且我和他交流并没有困难
is Edgar
and he was not getting it.
然后今天
And then today
他交给我一个不可思议的故事
he turned in this amazing story.
尼克 事实上你应该读一下
Nick, actually,
you should read this.
作家不读别人的作品  我们只写作
Writers don't read--
we write.
杰西卡 戴 把这个叫做“必读文章”
Jessica Day calls it
"A must read."
看看这个封面
Look at that font.
这个业余爱好者是哪个时代的?
What is this amateur hour?
至少也应该用帕拉提诺体（一种西文字体）啊
At least use Palatino.
晚上好  各位
Good evening, everyone.
或者我应该说早上好?
Or should I say morning?
你好 温斯顿
Hey, Winston.
你们谁有龙舌兰?
Do you guys have any agave?
我们这儿也许有扁豆糖浆
We might have some
pressed lentil syrup
在那个杂货壁橱里
in the mixin's cabinet.
多谢
Thank you.
哦 我的天哪
- Oh, my goodness.
好吧 呃
- Okay, uh...
好吧  你知道吗
- Okay, you know what?
嘿  你看
- Hey, look...
我只是感觉到 你的小弟弟在向我致敬...
I just felt the
side, the side
无论如何  这真是
- anyway, so it's...
我不是故意的
- I didn't mean to...
没关系  只是
It's fine, it's...
靠边  立刻
Other way, now.
我要揍你  杰克
- I will fight you, Jack.
哦  别再这样
- No, not again.
别  不!
Not... no!
不!  别挡路  杰西卡!
- No!
- Jump out the way, Jessica?
你有病吧
What the hell is wrong
with you just waving
像个傻子似的挥舞你“那玩意”?
that thing around
like an idiot?
♪ NEW GIRL字幕组 百度NEWGIRL吧?
♪翻译 木头 妹子是浮云 苏凉 橘子糖 ♪
校对 月潇 木头 橘子糖 creep93
压制 creep93
亲们  听这个
Guys, listen to this.
"白天的时候  我是个管道工"
"By day, I'm a plumber.
"晚上的时候  我是个跟踪者"
By night, I'm a stalker."
啊  你读这篇文章了
You read it.
"我坐在灌木丛里
"I sit in the bushes
身穿一套蒙面黑影装 跟踪我的猎物"
wearing a gimp costume,
stalking my prey."
他是我教到的第一个
He's the first
person I got
用第一人称叙事的
to use first person narrative.
我是一个天才老师
♪ I'm an amazing teacher.
非常给力  继续  我被吸引住了
- Very engaging, keep going.
- I'm hooked.
好的  "我的猎物是一只鹿"
Okay, "My prey is a deer.
"她的眼睛很大  非常大"
"Her eyes are big, too big.
"在她有机会眨一下她的大眼睛之前"
"Before she can blink
those big eyes,
"我扎伤了她"
"I'm stabbing her.
"我扎了一下又一下"
"I stab and stab.
"我喜欢扎她"
I love stabbing."
听起来他喜欢扎这个动作
Sounds like
he likes stabbing.
"在扎完之后"
"After all the stabbing..."
这是个重复动作  但是
It's repetitive, but...
"我用"
"...I wash my hands
"她深红色的血液洗手?!"
in her dark red blood"?!
听这个细节
Listen to that detail.
这个人是个精神病
This man is psychotic.
这只是个小说
It's fiction.
根本就没有黑影装这种东西
There's no such thing
as a gimp costume.
不 黑影装不是YY出来的 而是真实存在的
- No, gimp costume's a real thing.
- That's a real thing.
你之前曾经见我穿过一次
You've seen me in one before.
我认为你不应该
I just don't think
you should be in a room
每周和这个变态同处一室两天
with this creep, twice a week.
这是不安全的
It is not safe.
你是在担心我吗  米勒?
Are you worried about me,
Miller?
是的  我有一点担心你
Yeah, I'm a little worried
about you.
而且如果你们不采取什么措施的话
And if you won't do
那么我就要
anything about it,
then I'm taking
自己着手来处理这件事情了
into my own hands.
我做了一些调查
I'm doing a little
investigation.
调查?  拜托
Investigating? Please.
你只是刚刚在google上搜索了他的名字
You're just gonna
Google his name.
我要做得调查远不止那个
I am way beyond that.
可是你正在在google搜索里输入他的名字
You're typing his
name into Google.
我们都能看到你的屏幕  兄弟
We can all see the screen.
See the screen, dude.
这是一个私人调查!
This is a private investigation!
你是在   我想跟你谈一下
Are you... I wanted
to talk to you
关于
about the...
那个让我后悔的接触
regrettable contact
与希希的
between Cece's...
她下面的
her-her down there
和我的
and my, uh...
我身体的一部分
my parts.
你明显对她有反应
You practically
shish-kebabbed her.
我是不是应该为这个道歉?
Is this something
I should apologize for?
忘了吧  兄弟
Just let it go, man.
你活塞（晨勃）戳到她了
You pogo'd her.
不好意思  你刚才说什么，活塞？
I'm sorry,
what did you say, "pogo"?
我没有  呃  我听到了
- I didn't, um...
- I heard
"活塞"  那是什么?
"Pogo" -- what is that?
听着  温斯顿  好吧
Look, Winston, fine.
这就是我们如何称呼你的
It's what we call what you did
今天早上的行为的  行吗?
this morning, okay?
那只是  只是快速记忆的简称
It's a short...
it's a shorthand.
为什么你用这个简称称呼我  施密特
Why do you have
a shorthand, Schmidt,
因为这个经常发生?
because it happens so often?
你戳过我一次
You pogo'd me once.
你戳过杰茜两次  嘿  那跟性冲动没有关系
- You pogo'd Jess twice.
- Hey, it's not sexual.
尼克从来没有被直接的戳过
Nick's never been
pogo'd directly.
你确实戳过他的比萨一次  那是  好吧  顺便一说
You did get his pizza one
time... which, by the way,
不是这个话题  你怎么从来都没有感觉到过?
is a whole nother debate--
how did you not feel that?
让我直说吧
Let me get this straight--
你们坐在一起谈论这个?
you guys sit around
and talk about this?
你的小弟弟还能换台
Your penis actually
changed the channel,
呃  看黑熊队比赛的那次
uh, when we were watching
the Bears game once.
你不觉得我  尼克和杰茜
You don't think
me, Nick and Jess
在你背后讨论你吗
talk about you behind your back?
因为我们就是在讨论你
Because we do.
比任何人的次数都多
You have more pogos than anyone.
你完全的误解了POGO这个词
You are completely
misusing the word pogo.
你是外号之王
You are the pogo king.
外号王
Pogo king.
外号王?
Pogo king?
现在我们来谈谈你们的创意比喻作业
So I wanted to talk about your
creative imagery assignments.
哇哦，童鞋们
Wow, guys.
我感觉我就像被一场巨大的闪闪发亮的
I really felt like I was buried
粉状的形容词雪崩
under a giant, gleaming, powdery
给埋了
avalanche of adjectives.
不是故意打断的，我听说
Don't mean to interrupt,
I just hear you're the best
你是最棒的成人教师？
- teacher of adults?
哦，不是
- Oh, no.
我想这里还能再加一个人不？
- I wonder if there's room for one more?
不行
- No!
大家好，我是朱利叶斯.派伯伍德
How you guys doing?
I'm Julius Pepperwood.
现在不行，好吗？
- Not now, okay?
我干过条子，干过海军
- I'm an ex-cop, ex-Marine.
我来这是为了学怎么写短篇小说的
I'm here to learn how
to write short fiction.
好吧，朱利叶斯，那就
Oh, okay, Julius, just...
找个座位坐下，还有
take a seat and, um,
小点声
keep small.
我来自芝加哥
I'm from Chicago.
薄皮披萨？不滴，谢谢了
Thin-crust pizza?No, thank you.
哥是芝加哥来的
I'm from Chicago.
那么，为了下面一个有趣的后续活动
So, for a fun follow-up...
抱歉，我来晚了
- Sorry, I'm late.
没事，埃德加
- No, problem, Edgar.
我们要重温一下这些
We're just going over our
你们描述的形象
- descriptive imagery.
抱歉，老师
- I'm sorry, dear,
我听不见你声音
I can't hear you.
派伯伍德先生？
Mr. Pepperwood?
你要是不介意，我想离你近点
I'm gonna move closer,
if you don't mind.
不，你不用过来……呆在那
No, you don't have to go...
stay over there.
你好，伙计
How you doing, pal?
我是朱利叶斯.派伯伍德
- I'm Julius Pepperwood.
埃德加
- Edgar.
你干啥呢？
What are you doing?
你要是不介意，我想问问
If you don't mind me asking,
你为啥今天迟到了，埃德加？
why are you late
today, Edgar?
呃，堵车了，真要命（kill me英文直译是杀了我）
Uh, traffic, it
really killed me.
要你命？(杀了你？)
- It killed you?
派伯伍德先生
- Mr. Pepperwood.
你是说堵车捅了你一刀？
Would you say that
it stabbed you?
再说一遍？
Say that again?
把眼镜拿下来怎么样?
How about glasses on or off?
老师？要是我一直带着墨镜
Teach, if I keep them on,
看起来像个坏男孩不？
- am I a bad boy?
嘿！
- Hey.
好吧，亲，我不戴了
All right, honey,
I'll take them off.
哇哦，摘了眼镜看那个蓝裙子又是另一种样子了
Whoa, that's a whole different
lens to see that blue dress.
不是
No.
好了，让我们重新集中精神
Okay, let's refocus.
我们谈谈关于
Um, let's talk
about the, um,
冲突的四种分类
four classifications
of conflict.
我们上周谈了
We talked about it
last week.
课本上有
It's in the workbook, um...
任何人想说一下吗？
Anybody want to help me?
四类冲突？
Four classifications
of conflict?
有人吗？
Anybody?
Anybody...
还没有人在办公时间签名
So, no one has signed up for
office hours and I just want
我就想让你们知道可以和我说任何事
you to know that you can talk
to me about anything.
再见（西班牙语都出来了）
- Adios.
任何事
- Anything at all.
没关系亲，你穿工作服也很帅气
Nothing, man, you look good in your Dockers.
什么?  没什么  我是朱利叶斯·派珀伍德
What? Nothing happened.I'm Julius Pepperwood.
你走把
Let it go.
唔
Whoops.
你为什么要这么做  -不是我  是风吹的
- Why did you do that?- The wind.
不  不  不  不
No, no,no, no, no, no.
没什么事吧?
Is everything all right?
是的  没事  我们很好  兄弟
Yeah, everything's good.Oh, everything's fine, bro.
现在是什么情况
What's happening right now?
对不起  埃德加  我真的
Sorry, Edgar,um, I really
很喜欢你写的故事
loved your story.
我想给你一些笔记
Um, I wanted to give you
你什么时候有时间
some notes-- is there any time
都可以来...办公时间行嘛?
you could come in...to office hours?
好啊  这样太好了
Yeah, that be really cool.
我太兴奋了
I'm really excited.
我随时都有空  所以...
Um, I'm available anytime, so...
我查下我的日程安排
- I'll check my calendar.- Yup.
这里没有信号
Can't get service around here.
星期三我要去鸟店
Wednesday I got to go to the bird store.
星期三下午怎么样?
Uh, what about Wednesday afternoon?
他是我叔叔
He's my uncle.
嘿  温斯顿  欢迎回家
Hey, Winston,I'm glad you're home.
我知道我的外号了
I know what my pogo is.
我跳舞像条海蛇
It's that I dance kind of like a sea snake.
的确像  但是跟外号差远了  施密特
Yeah, not even close, Schmidt.
你说什么...我知道  就是这个
What are you talk...I know this it, man.
是我在你们洗澡的时候随便闯进来吗?
Is it that I barge into people's showers?
是我的毛毛虫眉毛  快看
It's my caterpillar eyebrows-- well, look.
没了
They're gone.
尼克  你做的太过分了  太过分了
Nick, you've gone way too far!Way too far.
如果你是来着埃德加的笔记的  你来晚了
Well, if you're here for Edgar's notebook, you're too late.
笔记在哪?
Where's the notebook?
尼克!
Nick!
我的准则一是什么?
What's my one rule?
别偷你的毛线
It's to not steal your yarn.
不要偷我的毛线  兄弟
Don't steal my yarn, man.
这是我的准则一
It's my one thing.
但是你要看一下他的笔记里的东西
But look at what was inside of his notebook.
好吧  他不过是在课堂上涂鸦了而已  尼克
Okay, he was doodling in class, Nick.
滴血的凶器 ?
Weapons, dripping with blood?
这根本就不是涂鸦
That is not a doodle.
你是谁  涂鸦警察?
What are you, the doodle police?
根本没有涂鸦警察  好吗           -真的吗?
- There's no doodle police, are there?- Really?
我不敢相信你还是不相信我
I can't believe you still don't believe me.
杰茜卡
Jessica...
作品D
Exhibit D.
他画的
He did this.
我要去埃德加家寻找更多的证据
I'm going to Edgar's house,I'm looking for more proof.
不行  尼克  你不能监视跟我有关的
No, Nick, you're not spying on the one student
任何一个学生
that I have a connection with.
我有地址    -不行
- I have the address right here.- No.
把地址给我...   -不给!
- Give me the...- No!
我已经记住地址了        -好吧  我也要跟你一起去
- I have the address memorized.- Fine, then I'm coming, too.
当你因为非法进入民宅被逮捕的时候去保释你
To bail you out of jail when you get arrested for trespassing.
好吧  你会亲眼看见我说的是对的    -好!
- Fine, then you'll see that I was right. - Fine!
你也会看到谁先到那里
And you'll also see who gets there first.
或者我们可以一起开车去
Maybe we should take one car.
为了环保
Just, like, for the environment.
是的  听起来不错  我们可以一起开车去
Yeah, that makes sense--we can drive together.
好!  -好!
- Fine!- Fine!
是我的痣  对吧
It's my mole, isn't it?
好吧  看着它消失吧
Well, consider it gone.
玩儿蛋去吧 烂外号
Game, set, pogo.
冷静点  伙计  不是因为你的痣
Chill out, man, it's not your mole.
赶紧告诉我吧  这已经是最坏的了
Just tell me,this is the worst.
这不是最坏的  施密特  最坏的是
This is not the worst, Schmidt-- the worst
你知道
is actually knowing.
你知道你的朋友们
Knowing that your friends
每晚都坐在一起
sit around every single night
讨论你的外号
talking about your pogo.
是什么外号?
What's a pogo?
他的眉毛没吓到你吗?
Those brows don't freak you out?
才不会  我看到过更恶心的
Nah, I've seen worse.
标签就是当你离开房间的时候
A pogo is what your friends talk about
你的朋友们背着你讨论你词语
when you leave the room.
噢  像你那藤壶般的脚趾甲?
Oh, like your barnacle toenails?
啊  (ˇˍˇ）
Uh... sh...
你们说的是我的脚趾甲?
You guys talk about my toenails?
绝对没有...
Never...
谈论你的脚趾甲...施...施密特
talk about your toenails, Sch... Schmidt.
我知道我的脚趾甲是有些盘旋崎岖
I know my toenails are a little rugged.
散发着木头的清香
Woodsy.
我说  我觉得你有这样的脚趾甲
I mean, I have never wondered
爬棕榈树都无障碍啊
if you could shimmy up a palm tree.
但是这是因为我的脚上角质太多的原因啊  我说...
But it's because I have a keratin surplus, I mean...
他们没有那么糟吧  看这些小东西
They're not that bad,look at these things.
啊!施密特!   -太恶心了你!
- Aah! Schmidt!- Ew!
它看上去就像一把打开的瑞士军刀
It looks like an open Swiss Army knife.
大部分都很硬  但是其中有一些却是非常柔软的
Most of them are hard, but one of them is really, really soft.
我知道  我知道  你们说说我的标签是什么
I know, I know, I know-- we'll just talk about what my pogo is.
我的标签是啥?
What's my pogo?
是我说"锅"时的发音吗?
Is it the way I say "pan"?
呱  呱  呱
Pan, pan, pan.
听着  希希  这大部分都是我们公寓的事
Look, Cece, this is more of just a loft thing.
感谢你的幸运星你没有
Just thank your lucky stars that you don't have
钙化过度的脚趾甲!
calcified mongrel toes!
听上去就像堆死螃蟹
Things sound like a dang ol' crab.
就是这了
There it is.
假如有什么意外发生的话 我们需要对一个安全的暗号
If anything's gonna go down,we need a safe word.
不会有什么意外的 有意外也是我们搞砸的
Nothing's gonna go down unless we make it go down.
如果Pepperwood教会了我什么事的话  -没有Pepperwood这种东西
- If Pepperwood taught me anything - There's no Pepperwood.
没对好暗号之前绝对不能被抓到
Never get caught without a safe word.
我们的暗号是"杏"
We're gonna go with "apricot."
这也太普通了 我们需要
That's way too normal.We need to, like,
用一些古怪的词 像"巨龙拖鞋"这样的
go with something weird,like "dragon slippers."
神马?  -我平常说了太多的"杏"了
- What?- I use "apricot" too much in my normal life.
为神马你会说那么多的"杏"?
Why do you use "apricot" so much?
那你说我应该叫它们什么-"甜蜜香浓球"?
What am I supposed to call them-- "sweet tangy balls"?
杰茜卡 求你不要叫它们"甜蜜香浓球"
Don't call them "sweet tangy balls," Jessica.
好吧 但是这就是为什么我们不能用...
Well, that's why we can't use...
尼克 尼克
Nick... Nick...
尼克 噢!
Nick, oh!
嘘 快来
Shh! Come on...
尼克 -请叫我朱利叶斯·派珀伍德
- Nick..-  Call me Julius Pepperwood, please.
你太荒谬了
You look ridiculous.
如果我们不被人发现
If we're hiding from people,
我叫你什么有什么不同?    -我望风
- why does it matter what I call you?- I got my eyes
你紧随我后     -不 不 不 这到底是啥意思?
- and you get my six.- No, no, what does this mean?
我十分肯定这个... -它的意思是"自行车靠右"
- I'm pretty sure this...- This means "right turn bicycle."
不对 我十分肯定它的意思是"停止行动"    -它的意思是"靠右行"
- No, I'm pretty sure this means "stop...- " It means "right turn."
尼克 说人话
Nick, seriously--use your words.
别用这些该死的反恐特警队的暗号   -好的 我说人话
- Don't use freaking SWAT sign language.- Okay, these are my words.
噢!
Oh!
杏  杏  杏
Apricot, apricot,apricot.
闭嘴闭眼
Close your mouth,close your eyes.
埃德加跟他妈住在一起  当然了
Edgar lives with his mother.Of course he does.
那又怎样? 许多正常人都跟他们妈妈住在一起
So? A lot of normal people live with their mothers.
我的叔叔兰迪就跟他妈住在一起
Like my Uncle Randy.
那是因为他连独自去公园都不敢    -他早就不怕了
- He can't go near parks.- He was cleared.
你能不能...
You've got to...
杏!杏!
Apricot! Apricot!
快跑!
Get over here now!
噢卖糕的
- Oh, my God.- Oh, my God.
他在麻布袋里装了什么?
What's in that duffel bag?
在故事中他是个水管工人
He's the plumber from the story.
我之前怎么就没意识到?      -知道不听尼克言的结局了吧?
- How did I not see this before?- What was I saying?
我的神 你说对了    -我知道  再说一遍
- Oh, my God, you were right.- Yes, say that again,
再说一遍 -你说对了你说对了 你是预言大帝
- say that again. You were right, you were right, you were right about everything.
别忘了你说过的话!      -我的上帝
- Don't ever forget you're saying it!- Oh, my God,
不敢相信你说对了     -我是预言大帝!
- I can't believe you were right.- I was a right about everything!
那个袋子里究竟装了什么?
What the hell is in that duffel bag?
我咋知道  -不 尼克
- I don't know.- No, Nick.
尼克 你要害死我们     -悄悄的就不会被发现了
- Nick, you're gonna get us killed.- Let's get down.
尼克 尼克!
Nick... Nick...
嘘
Shh.
♪我是如此兴奋...(杰茜的手机铃声)
♪ I'm so excited...
噢 我的...杰茜卡 关掉
Oh, my... Jessica, turn it off.
赶快关掉! 噢 上帝 那是埃德加  -我该怎么做?
- Turn it off! Oh, my God, it's Edgar.- What do I do?
关掉...给我
You turn it... Here.
赶快关掉 我不知道怎么弄    -给我
- Turn it off. I don't know how to do this. - Okay.
我的上帝  赶快离开这儿
Oh, my God. Get the hell out of here.
杰茜 你在搞神马?
Jess, what are you doing?
你太笨了  这里有这么多出口
That is ridiculous. There was plenty of room.
但是这样看上去是个好主意
It seemed like a good idea.
为神马你非要钻进货车底下去?
Why would you go under a van?
赶紧走吧
Let's leave.
保持安静...-你们绝对不会相信刚刚发生的事情
Keep still...-You will not believe what just happened.
尼克说对了  -是的 我说对了
- Nick was right.- I was right.
我的神 你的眉毛怎么了?
Oh, my God, what happened to your eyebrows?
你看上去就像奥黛丽·赫本嘛
You look like Audrey Hepburn.
难道我们没有工业规模的切纸机?
Don't we own an industrial-size paper cutter?
啊哈  -随便你们好了
- Ugh! - Oh, whatever.
这究竟是什么?
- What the hell is that?
离吃饭的地方太近了！
- So close to the eating area!
温斯顿说你们都拿我的精致的脚趾甲开玩笑
Winston told me that you guys make fun of my gremlin toenails.
你们叫它们"叮叮当小脚丫""半人马战靴"神马神马的
That you call them "clickety- clacks" or "centaur boots."
你脑子出问题了吧 温斯顿?
What is wrong with you, Winston?
我脑子有毛病?  因为这就是我的标签
What is wrong with me? Besides my pogo.
我说过了   我只是说出了我的想法
I told him.It just kind of popped out.
你知道这种感觉吧 温斯顿
You understand what that's like, right, Winston?
好吧 知道嘛 别表现的就像
Okay, you know what? Don't act like
我们不会背着你谈论你们一样
we don't talk about you two behind your backs.
因为我们确实会  你们都有标签 我的朋友们
Because we do. You both have pogos, my friends.
好吧 让我们先深呼吸一下再问我们自己
Okay, let's take a deep breath and ask ourselves
这场谈话是否真的值得结束我们的友谊
if this conversation is worth ruining our friendships over.
告诉我我的标签
Tell me my pogo.
我必须知道你们给我贴的标签
I need to know my pogo.
你们必须告诉我  我能接受  尽管说吧!
You guys need to tell me.I can take it. Lay it on me!
好吧  上升到了公寓事件了  是我的派的问题吗?
You know, it's kind of a loft thing.Is it my pies?
他们太酸了吗?
Are they too tart?
派不能成为标签 好吗
Pies can't be a pogo, okay?
我的考拉爪  这才是标签!
My koala claws,now that's a pogo!
至少你还可以吧你的标签藏在鞋子里
At least you can hide your pogo in a shoe.
他们给你的小弟弟制造鞋子-这就是他们所说的裤子!
They make shoes for your penis--they're called pants!
告诉我我的标签 -杰茜卡 不要
- Tell me my pogo.- Jessica, no.
告诉我我的标签!  -你就是个万事通
- Tell me my pogo!- You're a know-it-all!
超级万事通   -还是最烂的
- Huge know-it-all.- The worst.
噢  我成了世界最烂超级万事通?
Oh, I'm the worst know-it-all in the world?
拜托 别说的这么夸张
Please. Hate hyperbolic speak. Please.
现在你们都知道了你们的标签  你们都知道了
Now you know your pogo,you truly know it all.
我又一次成了自作聪明的笨蛋
There I go being a smart-ass again.
这个可能就是我的标签
I mean, that, that could be my pogo.
还有一个没有呢
And then there was one.
噢  不  不  不  我很肯定你们有
Oh, no, no, no, I'm sure that you guys have stuff
背着我嘲笑我的事情
you laugh at me behind my back.
我们不会嘲笑你的标签 尼克
We don't laugh about your pogo, Nick.
是的 我们更加比较担心你
Yeah. We're worried about you.
你们担心我?
You're worried about me?
我们担心你你做不好
We're worried that you're not gonna make it.
做不好什么?     -正常人都能做好的事情
- Make it to what? - Just in general.
因为你不知道怎么照顾自己
'Cause you don't take care of yourself.
有时候我会把维生素碾碎了
Sometimes I'll crumple up vitamins
放在你的食物中
and I'll put them in your food.
我们轮流从你把裤子放到烘干机之前
We all take turns sneaking money into your pants pockets
拿出裤子口袋里面的钱
before we put them in the dryer.
是吗 ?  好吧  希望你们开心了
Yeah? Well,I hope you're happy.
所有人的标签都见光了
The pogos are out.
公寓活力被你们毁了
The loft dynamic is ruined.
我的娃娃音怎么样?
But what if I talk like a baby?
你还是很辣  我们都会这么说
You're still hot. That's all we're gonna talk about.
一个小北鼻哦!
A tiny little baby!
请别再表演了
Cut into these, please.
哇噢  哇噢  哇噢  哇呜
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,whoa, whoa, whoa!
噢...梯子
Oh...! A ladder...
这下好了
That'll do.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
噢  这可不好
Oh, this is bad.
这样实在不好
Oh, this is... this is very bad.
噢  我的亲娘  不要这样
Oh, no, oh, no-- no, no-no-no-no-no-- oh, God, oh, God.
♪ 我是如此兴奋...
♪ I'm so excited...
哈喽
Hello.
杰茜  他想杀死你       -神马?
- Jess, he wants to kill you!- What...?
我现在正在他的窝棚里    -啥?
- I am in his shed right now- What?
墙上贴满了你的画像
And there are drawings on the wall of you,
画着血淋淋的凶器
and bloody weapons
和鼓鼓的眼睛
and googly eyes.
鼓鼓的眼睛看上去是蛮性感   但是还有...
Googly eyes are actually kind of sexy, but that's beside...
杰茜  我绝不会让你跟这个人独处一室的
Jess, I will not let you be in a room alone with this guy.
在他写的故事中你就是鹿
You're the deer in his story.
他想杀了你
He wants to kill you.
你就是鹿 你就是鹿 你就是鹿
You're the deer, you're the deer, you're the deer.
我在学校  正在备课...
I'm at school and I'm doing office hours...
赶紧走  好  我会跟你保持通话
Get out now! Okay, I'll just,I'll just keep you on the line,
等我说暗号  好吗
and then I'll say the safe word, okay?
我像这样...杏!救命!
I'll just say it like...Apricots! Apricots!
很好  当你看到埃德加就这么说
Good. Yeah, yeah, that's what you say if you see Edgar.
杏! 是真的  杏!
Apricots! Really, apricots!
噢 不  好的 好的 别说了
Oh, no. Okay, okay, stop it.
我知道他在你那儿了
He's there. Okay.
我还以为你会说"巨龙拖鞋"
I thought it was gonna be"dragon slippers."
是我来的时间不对还是...?
Is this a bad time or...?
没有 没有  只是杂货店的老板听力有问题
No, no, no, no.I just have a deaf grocer.
杏!杏!
Apricots! Apricots!
和 黄油
And butter.
我来了
I'm coming.
哦 吼吼
Oh! Ho-ho!
欢迎办公时间到来
Welcome to office hours.
Um...
-我找到我的结局了
-是吗？
- I found my ending.
- Yeah?
虽然这结局很冒险 而且
It's pretty risky. I'm not sure
我不确定我能否写好
I'm gonna be able
to get away with it.
(Chuckles)
哦
(Grunts)
Oh!
记不记得你告诉我
Remember when you told me
写小说的人物时可以依据真实人物
to base my characters
on people from my own life?
我写的时候依据了你
Well, I based one on you.
-真荣幸啊
-然后我意识到
- So flattered.
- And then I realized
这个故事只有一个结局
that there was only one way
for the story to end.
你必须死
You need to die.
危险了 危险了
(Softly):
Apricot, apricot.
不 喂
No! ♪ Hey...!
喂 喂 喂 喂
♪ Uh, uh-uh-uh...!
你拿出了笔记本哦
♪ Look at that notebook.
(Groaning)
你说过 好的文学作品会让人惊讶
You said, "Great literature
is surprising."
还有什么能比让主角死掉更让人惊讶的事呢
What's more surprising than
killing your main character?
不如这样吧 听我说 要不
What about this--
go with me-- what if, um,
要不就让我的角色活着吧 然后这本书继续
what if my character lives
and the book just goes on?
当别人以为要结束了的时候
Imagine coming to the end
of the book,
其实还没有结束
and then just finding
a lot more book.
惊讶吧
Surprise.
啊哦
- ♪ I'm so excited
- Um, oh.
-我昨天也听到这首歌了
- ♪ And I just can't hide it...
- I heard that song yesterday.
这段时间到处都放这首歌
This song is everywhere
these days.
你昨天在我家里吗？
Were you at my house?
-谢谢 再见了您
-别
- Okay, thank you. Good-bye.
- No.
-别别
-我必须走了
- No! No!
- I have to go... right now.
危险消除 危险消除
Apricot's leaving!
太好了我真高兴你还活着
Oh, good.
I'm so happy you're alive.
在里面呆着 锁上门
Okay, stay inside
and lock the door.
我现在就去 我去保护你
I am coming. I am going
to protect you... (Groans)
尼克？ 胡椒木！尼克？
Nick?! Pepperwood! Nick!?
小偷？他可不是小偷
Burglar?! He's not a burglar.
他是来自芝加哥的 朱利叶斯.派伯伍德
He's Julius Pepperwood
from Chicago.
把他抬进屋吧
Let's get him
in the house.
我肯定得被论功行赏
The D.A.'s gonna have my badge
for this.
不要 放开他
No! Get off of him!
你要杀了他 那你也杀了我吧
You kill him, you kill me, too!
放开我的埃德加
Get away from my Edgar!
我的眼睛啊
My eyes! Oh!
我水灵灵的大眼睛啊
My giant eyes!
你们以为我是谋杀犯？
You thought I was
a murderer?
你们以为我真心杀人了？
You thought I was a
murderer of people?
你不是说你要杀了我吗？
You said you were gonna
kill me, so I don't know.
你的角色  在我小说里的角色
Your character...
in my graphic novel.
-他可是个优秀的艺术家
- He's an excellent artist.
-但是你那些画
- Okay, but your drawings,
都没有眼睛啊
they don't have any eyes.
-我讨厌画眼睛 太奇怪了
- Hate drawing eyes. It's weird.
-他画不好眼睛
- He can't draw eyes.
这回说得通了
There's a reason for everything.
那那个帆布袋是怎么回事？
What about the duffel bag?
不许问帆布袋的事
Don't ask about the duffel bag!
婊子
Bitch.
-哇哦 哇哦
- Whoa, whoa!
-哇哦 哥们
- Whoa! Hey, man.
就当是赞扬你把 哥们
Hey, take this
as a compliment, pal.
你的故事太真实了
Your stories are so real.
是因为你教的好啊
Well, it's because
what you taught me.
你听课了？
You listened?
当然听了 你是个好老师
Well, of course I listened.
You were a good teacher.
直到你认为我是个杀人犯还闯进我的仓库
Until you thought I was a murderer
and you broke into my shed.
你是我最好的学生
Aw! You were my favorite
student until
直到我以为你是个杀人犯
I thought you were
a murderer.
-哎
- Ah...
-你的儿子真的是个好作家
- Your son's a really great writer.
-他不是我儿子
- He's not my son.
-你开玩笑呢吧
- Oh! Are you kidding?!
真的吗你
Really?!
我服了你俩了
Real nice, you two.
亲下宝贝
Come here, baby.
哦 天哪 你闻起来像华夫饼
Mm! God, you smell
like waffles.
我爱死你了 你刚刚做了华夫饼吗？
I love it. Did you just
make some waffles?
-你想把我吃干净吗？
-是啊 我想
- Want to eat me up?
- Yes, I do.
里面见 我去拿帆布袋
I'll meet you inside.
I'm gonna get the duffel bag.
-好 去吧
-好嘞
- Yes, do.
- Okay.
-嗨 尼克
-嗨
- Hey, Nick.
- Hey.
你在干嘛呢？
What are you doing up?
照顾照顾我自己
Just taking care of myself.
你是在培根上面放黄油吗？
Are you putting butter on bacon?
我不想让他们粘锅
I don't want it
to stick to the pan.
好吧 你有没有...?
Okay, did you...?
太棒了
Great.
培根就是需要
It's just what bacon needs,
更多的脂肪么
more fat.
还有盐
And salt.
-这是什么？
-先别看 我还没写完呢
- What's this?
- Don't read that. I'm not finished...
《僵尸侦探——朱利叶斯.派伯伍德》？
"Julius Pepperwood:
Zombie Detective"?
他杀的所有人都已经死了
All his murder victims
are already dead,
所以他可能不需要侦探 我还没想好呢
so they obviously don't need
a detective. I'm working on it.
-“一个漆黑的炎热的夜晚”
-别念了
- "The night was inky hot."
- Don't do this.
“她大踏步的走进他的办公室，她心怀目的， 内心平静..
"She strode into his office with
a sense of purpose, place,
再来个词 问号”
another word here,
question mark."
我还在找另一个有“心”的词
I'm looking for another
"P" word there.
“她的僵尸腿，一个跟头能翻十万八千里”
"She had zombie legs
that went on for miles.
“那僵尸腿能让你的牙齿陷进去”
"They were the kind of legs
you could sink your teeth into.
“如果算上他的帽子的话，派伯伍德有两个朋友”
"Pepperwood had two friends--
one, if you count his hat.
“另外一个是他的“星期五”女孩，杰西卡 夜”
The other was his gal Friday,
Jessica Night."
不是你哦 杰茜
It's not you, Jess.
“她身材矮小，并不勇敢”
"She was small in stature,
but not in spunk.
“而且还很自以为是的觉得自己什么都懂”
And a super annoying
know-it-all."
晚上好
Good evening.
好啊
Hello.
哦 培根
Oh, bacon.
你从哪来啊？
Where the hell
did you come from?
我从我屋来啊
I came from my room.
不是吧 我怎么没听见你脚指甲敲地的声呢？
No, I didn't hear the pitter-
patter of your disgusting feet.
我剪了 泡脚确实有用
I cut my toenails.
Yeah, the soaking really worked.
看看吧 他们美不美
Look at that.
They're gorgeous now.
-我脚马上小一号了
-着火了
- Went down a full shoe size.
- Guys! Fire!
- Whoa, whoa!
- Oh, my God!
大家淡定 快找火警
Everybody relax!
Call a fireman!
-你打电话给火警啊
-我就是火警
- You call the fireman!
- I'm the fireman.
你不能用水浇灭油起的火！
You can't put out a grease fire
with water!
你得让他隔绝空气
You have to smother it!
你咋不早说
Why didn't you say
that before?!
我不想自以为是
I don't want
to be a know-it-all!
-大傻子
-闭嘴
- You're so stupid!
- Shut up!
-哇哦
-好样的
- Whoo! Oh!
- Nice!
太棒了
Yes!
牛逼啊 小伙子
Amazing, my man! Whoa.
Whoa.
说实话 我没以为你能抱我
Honestly, I didn't know you were
gonna put your arm around me.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你在着火的时候还支了“小帐篷”
Oh, you put up your pup tent
in front of the fire.
我不是故意的
It's involuntary.
这其实是肾上腺素
It is a combination
of adrenaline
和良好环境的结合产生的
and great circulation.
你以后拜托别没事就拥抱我了
And I'd appreciate it if you
don't just hug me randomly!
那很奇怪...
That's weird and...!
你们有没有注意过温斯顿跑步啊？
You ever notice...
when Winston runs,
-他有点边跑边放屁的样子
- that he kinda farts while
he's running?      - Yes!
-听起来像是破飞机似的
-新标志
- Sounds like a jalopy.
- New pogo.
我们有了个新的顶级标签啊
Oh, we got a great
new pogo!
边跑边放屁
He farts when he runs!
欢迎亲们踊跃留言，字幕会在NEWGIRL吧第一时间更新O(∩_∩)O